How to tie a string to a model
Today's little trick is to tie a string to a model
Now you can see that the 3D window is a breastplate
Other panels have been simulated on the model
The place behind this pin
Fixed with a transparent panel
Then change the transparency of this panel fabric to 0
The panel can be hidden in the 3D window
Start making the string effect below
These panels can be selected before making
This string panel does not need to be selected
Wait a moment to simulate
Right-click on the selected panel
After the freeze
See this panel is a transparent panel
But it still exists
In order to simulate it, there will be no conflict
You can right-click to reactivate
Let this panel not participate in simulation
Come down to the 2D window
See these basic lines on this panel
First use the hook outline tool
Can frame these circles
After the frame selection
Right-click on the selected line
Cut it and sew it
Because this circle needs to wait
So it is cut and sew
After cutting, use the adjustment panel tool
Select these panels
Move these small panels out
Convenient operation at the back
This side is also slightly moved out
Now move this panel down first
The following is to make the string effect
For string
First of all, this panel
You can move it in
The effect from the inside
Before making
You can put a inner line on this panel
Because it needs to be sewed with the tape
Use the edit panel tool
Measure its length
About 5 mm
Use the inner multidirectional tool
Create a 5 mm line
A little bit oblique
About 5 mm
Double-click to finish
After changing the number, you can slightly adjust
A little bit down
Because wait a minute
You have to sew the tape
Now after the number is drawn
You can see only one
Other panels can select the inner line
Then copy it
The following one
You can't just copy it here
Stick it out at a time
Because some panels are not the same
There will be deviations in the placement at a time
So you have to copy it one by one
After doing it
You can sew the panel below
Use the sewing tool
Sew it up
Show the panel
Switch to the texture surface
You can see that the panel is facing the other way around
You can choose it
Rotate it
Push it in
Then simulate
Now one is done
After done
Select this panel
Reduce its particle diameter
Can be adjusted to 5
Conflict can be adjusted to 1
Re-monit
Click the control button to simulate
Pause the simulation
One has been done
The following is the effect of binding the tape
Can be copied
Select the panel
Ctrl C Ctrl V copy and paste
Put it below
Adjust it
After that, sew it
Open the panel to show the inner line
Use the sewing tool
Sew in the 3D window
Click the two lines to sew
Good simulation
Pause the simulation
Use the adjustment panel tool
Select the panel
Then copy one
Rotate
Use the sewing tool
Sew in the 3D window
Good simulation
Now one is done
After done
You can see
It's coming out from the top
It should be in the bottom
So we can use the sewing tool
Select the sewing tool
You can go straight to the frame selection
Because the bottom panel is frozen
So I can't select it
After the frame selection
Click the sewing selection
Use the positioning ball to move in
The other side is also moved in
Then simulate
Pause the simulation
The side effect is good
Click the adjustment panel
Continue to use the same method below
Make the second one
Use the adjustment panel tool
Select the panel
After the frame selection
Copy
Ctrl C
Paste
Ctrl V
Then put the level below
After putting it down
Adjust the position
Then use the sewing tool
Sew in the 3D window
Good simulation
After done
Open the simulation
After the simulation
Use the same grid tool
Select the grid
Push it in
Push it in here too
Good simulation
Use the same method
You can continue to make it down
But when you do it below
You will find that the frame on top will be a little further
The frame below will be a little closer
So when you copy the selected version
After copying
You need a double-click to activate the center point
Then make the two panels a little shorter
After changing
Then use the sewing tool to sew
Simulate
Then use the grid tool
Push it in
Simulate
The same method
Take care of these panels below
Make all the rest of them
Good simulation
orama
Afteride
The
good tool
After a while
After all
There is still one
It should copy a board
Put it down
Adjust the location
Turn
After sewing, the bandage is all made, and then the texture is switched back to the thick texture display.
There should be one at the bottom.
The effect of tying the butterfly knot, we can prepare the butterfly knot in advance.
Increase it.
This is the butterfly knot that has been made in advance, put it on.
If the butterfly knot is made, you can go and see it.
Adjust the position.
After that, you can use a sewing thread or a sewing tool to fix it together.
Simulate.
The butterfly knot is almost done.
Turn off the window.
There needs to be an eye in the bandage.
The eye can be done with a button.
In the 3D window.
Find the button tool in the window.
Add a button on the board.
Probably in the middle.
Click to add a button.
After adding, it is default to be such a button.
The object window can be selected as a button.
In the attribute editor below, click on the shape.
You can choose a gas eye preset.
For example, the first one.
The first one will be relatively large.
You can modify the following specifications.
For example, change to 11.
11 is about the same.
Now one has been added.
You can select.
Select the move button tool.
Select the button.
Then copy and paste.
Ctrl C Ctrl V to the second button.
Click to add.
Then copy and paste.
The following buttons are the same.
It should be almost.
When pasting.
Press the Shift key.
The level goes down.
At the same time, press the right button.
Play the dialogue frame.
You can add more buttons at a time.
There should be a total of 7.
Add 7.
Then click to confirm.
After confirmation, you will find.
There are some distance deviations to the back buttons.
It may be the position of these gas eyes.
The structure itself is different.
So add more buttons at a time.
Its position is a little biased.
It doesn't matter.
You can select the button to delete.
Select the button above.
Copy one.
Then in the area near the button.
Click to add one.
Now half is added.
The other half can select all the buttons.
On the selected button above, right click.
Copy to the one-sided tune.
Click to copy quickly.
After the copy is completed.
Select these buttons.
You can turn off the collision.
Change the length of the line to a negative number.
For example, change it to a negative 2.
If you change the number of points,
The button will itself.
Sign in to this clip of the film.
This button is a negative 2.
May not be enough.
Can go a little more.
A negative 3.
About 2.5
Then select the button
Change its attribute
Type to metal effect
Select these small 7-eye plates
Because now it can be seen in the 3D window
You can apply a transparent plate material attribute
Make it transparent
Turn off the display internal line
Now the tape is a bit too thin
You can choose these tape plates
Increase its rendering thickness a little
For example, adjust to 1
The effect of 7-eye threading is done
Other plates can be activated
The above is the effect of threading
You can use this one
That's all
Thanks for watching
Please subscribe to my channel
And I will see you soon
Bye bye